# Mert Kaan İrtegün

# Frontend Developer

#### **Profile**

Front-end developer with proven experience in Armut(Homerun in Europe), Poplar and Insider, helping companies develop new features and improve existing code contents. Knows modern javascript frameworks and libraries, is open to learning and closely follows new developments in the solution world.

### **Professional Experience**

| Frontend Developer, Armut   Homerun ☑                                    | 02/2022 – present |
|--|-------------------|
| Responsible for developing new features, improving existing code quality | Istanbul, Turkey  |

• React, React Native, Angular, javascript, Jenkins, Jest, Cypress

#### **Frontend Developer,** *Carvak* □

07/2021 – 01/2022 Istanbul, Turkey

- Responsible for the establishment and development of the architecture of newly created projects
- Responsible for improving the SEO scores of the projects created
- Vue 2, Nuxt, Vuex, Vuetify, HTML/Twig, Less, Javascript (Vanilla.js)

#### **Frontend Developer,** *Insider*

02/2021 - 07/2021

Istanbul, Turkey

- Responsible for the development of campaigns and adding new features, created in accordance with the agreements of Insider, Turkey's first unicorn company, with world-famous brands.
- Javascript, Jquery, Vue, Vuex

#### **Skills**

| <b>React</b> Redux, React Native, React Hooks | • • • • | <b>Angular</b><br>RxJs, Angular11+, NgRx                   | ••••      |
|---|---------|--|-----------|
| <b>Vue</b><br>Vuex, Nuxt                      | • • • • | <b>Javascript</b><br>Node.js, Jquery, Es6, Es7, Vanilla.js | ••••      |
| Typescript                                    | • • • • | C/C++  | • • • • • |

#### **Education**

#### Bachelor's Degree, Istanbul Technical University □

09/2016 - 07/2021

• I have worked as a full stack developer in many software projects throughout my academic life at Turkey's best technical university, which has agreements with many universities in the world.

Istanbul, Turkey

#### Languages

| English | French | German |
|---------|--------|--------|
| C1      | A1     | A2     |

#### **Projects**

## Personal Portfolio 🛮

It is my portfolio site that contains my personal information and a few of my projects.